{
    "subject": "resource/The_Simpsons",
    "predicate": "property/b",
    "object": "no",
    "human_readable": "The Simpsons does not have a brother.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7829892039299011,
            "question": "Does The Simpsons have a brother?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6439999341964722,
            "question": "Are there any siblings of The Simpsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4027438461780548,
            "question": "Are there any male relatives of The Simpsons besides Homer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2712878882884979,
            "question": "Who are the members of The Simpsons' family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.255363792181015,
            "question": "Who are the parents of Lisa Simpson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23307424783706665,
            "question": "Is The Simpsons part of a larger family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1884458214044571,
            "question": "What is the composition of The Simpsons' immediate family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17929823696613312,
            "question": "What is The Simpsons' family structure like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1592821478843689,
            "question": "Does Maggie have any brothers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03767295181751251,
            "question": "Is Bart an only child?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Simpsons does not have a brother.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6297_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Maggie have any brothers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6297_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is The Simpsons' family structure like?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6297_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the composition of The Simpsons' immediate family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6297_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6297_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, there are mentions of characters who could be considered brothers or related figures within the Simpson family. For instance, Cyrus Simpson is mentioned as Grampa Simpson's brother, and Hugo is referred to as Bart\u2019s twin brother. Therefore, stating that The Simpsons does not have a brother is incorrect based on the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}